Yuan-Hong Liao

National Tsing Hua University Hsinchu City 30013, Taiwan

E-mail: andrewliao11@gmail.com

Personal Website: http://andrewliao11.github.io

Phone: +886 935327692

Interests

My research focuses on combining the visual and language representation through deep learning and apply it to tasks such as question answering and captioning. Recently, I've got immersed in deep reinforcement learning and intend to apply it on some visual tasks.

Education

National Tsing Hua University

B.S. Degree in EE• Sep. 2013 – Present

- Advisor: Prof, Min Sun
- Academic performance: Total GPA: 4.04/4.3, Last 60 GPA: 4.06/4.3, Rank: 8/105

University of California, Davis

Extension student in international English and Professional Programs • Jul. 2015 – Aug. 2015

• I received the scholarship from my school to attend UC Davis extension program.

Professional Experience

Vision Science Lab, NTHU

Research Assistance (RA) • Dev. 2015 – Present

- Conducting research on computer vision and machine learning, advised by Prof, Min Sun
- Proficient in image/video captioning and image/video question answering

Industrial Technology Research Institute

Research Intern • Mar. 2016 – Present

- Work in Computational Intelligence Technology Center in ITRI
- Present and survey on deep reinforcement learning
- Apply deep reinforcement learning on various application

Umbo Computer Vision Inc.

CV/ML Intern • Jun. 2016 – Present

• Focus on natural language object retrieval and image captioning, guided by Tingfan Wu

Skills

- C/C++, Python, Lua, Matlab, Java, and Javascript
- Windows, Linux/Unix experience
- Deep learning framework: Caffe, Torch, Tensorflow
- Experience in developing Android App, embedded system

Language

- Traditional Chinese (local speaker)
- English (GEPT High Intermediate level)

Honors and Awards

Excellent student scholarship of EECS college, NTHU • May. 2016

- Around 8 people are granted every year (<10%)